{
    "id": "e45064d5017f4413a48d788bb19d51fa",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… child can learn to sing.",
            "description": "Any and every can both be used to talk in general about all the members of a group.",
            "answers": [
                "Any",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Our birthdays are only a week …………………….",
            "description": "Apart can mean one from another.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "apart",
                "in between"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather was unpredictable but we went hiking ………………………………",
            "description": "Anyway means the same as anyhow. Both words mean nevertheless. ",
            "answers": [
                "anyway",
                "anyhow",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Which color would you like?’ ‘It doesn’t matter. …………………….. one.’",
            "description": "Any can mean this or that or the other.",
            "answers": [
                "Any",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "On the table there were books of ………………………… kind.",
            "description": "Every is similar to all, but all is not possible here because it is used with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "any",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t look …………………….. older than her daughter.",
            "description": "Any can modify comparatives. In this case, any is similar to at all.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Cooking breakfast is an ……………………. job.",
            "description": "Everyday means daily or common place. ",
            "answers": [
                "everyday",
                "every day",
                "everydays"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I read the newspaper ………………………….",
            "description": "Every day is synonymous with each day.",
            "answers": [
                "everyday",
                "every day",
                "everydays"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Was the movie ………………….. good?",
            "description": "This is similar to ‘at all’.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My hopes were …………………..",
            "description": "Rise can mean go up.",
            "answers": [
                "rising",
                "arising",
                "Rise can mean go up."
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The children were running …………………….. everywhere.",
            "description": "Round is used for movement in a circle or curve. Around can refer to movements that are not very definite.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "around",
                "round"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t …………………….. to understand his motives.",
            "description": "Seem is often used with can’t. Appear cannot be used like this.",
            "answers": [
                "seem",
                "appear",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}